In which case will you get it? If you have a
comprehensive car insurance policy,
okay? So, if you do
n't want to pay anything, you want to be completely free, you
want to have peace of mind that
you don't have to pay anything at the end of the day,
okay? You don't want to read in this article about
what all is covered, how much
percent depreciation is being charged,
hello friends, how are you all? Welcome back
to my channel, friends, there are
many things in an insurance policy, sometimes there is
confusion about
which parts will be covered
and which parts will not be covered,
right? So, today we will talk about that issue,
regarding our airbag system,
suppose someday the car meets with an accident
or some defect is found in it,
right, then it will have to be replaced,
now if we assume that it has to be replaced, then is
your airbag covered in our insurance policy or not, so
today we will talk about this issue,
if you guys like the video.
So please like, share the video and subscribe to the channel
friends, see
what is an airbag system, it is
related to your safety, right, now suppose there are
sensors in it, as you
all know, so as soon as these sensors
detect the movement, then your
airbag will open, which is
made for your protection, okay, so that your
life is safe, now what happens is that the
airbag will be
used only once, it is not that you can reuse it,
like if a tyre gets punctured, you can
reuse it again, okay, but in this case it is
not like that, you will have to
change the entire assembly of the airbag,
right, so now the question arises whether the
airbag is covered or not,
friends, look, for example,
I will tell you that when you
buy any thing, any product,
then what happens to it, there is a life
cycle, okay, so for example, suppose
you buy any thing in the first year, then
what does the company do in it  Depreciation is charged. Now, if it is the
second year, the percentage of
depreciation on it will increase. Now, in simple language, let me
tell you what depreciation is.
Whatever product you have purchased from the showroom, then
what will happen next year or the year after that, 3 years later,
its original price will fall,
right? So, this is your
depreciation and it
depends from company to company, product
to product, how much percentage of
depreciation will be charged, suppose in the first year it will be charged at 10,
next year it will be charged at 15, 20, 25, 30, this way it is
charged and it depends on your
insurance company, it will be charged on it and on
your product, right, now
what will happen in this case, for example,
you have plastic parts,
nylon parts, rubber parts,
for example, you have air bags,
tyre tubes etc. inside it, so
what will happen to you, the
depreciation will be charged on it  That depreciation will be charged
on 50%, the company which charges depreciation will
charge it on 50%, you heard it absolutely right, so
suppose you have to get it replaced, some
accident happens etc., then the company will pay
you whatever is due on 50% only,
right, now what will happen in this case,
they paid on 50% and you will have to pay on 50% from your pocket,
now in this thing you will see the
depreciation that has been charged and the
money that you will get, in which case will you get it, if
you have a comprehensive car insurance
policy, then okay, so if you do
not want to pay anything, you
want to be completely free, you want to have peace of mind
that you do not have to pay any money at the end of the day,
okay, you do not want to read in this paragraph
what all is being covered,
how much percentage of depreciation is being charged, then for this
you will have to pay a little extra
premium and in that you will have to take add-ons,
add-ons are covered, I have already
told you in many videos, in this
you will have to take an add-on which
comes with your RO depreciation  By the name of and
you must have heard the most famous one is Ro Dep, okay, so
if you have Zero Tap, then
under Ro Dep you will not have to pay any money,
so the company will provide you the facility of Ro Dep
under it, in the first
5 years, in that 5 years you will have to pay
Zero Tap, that is, you will have to pay Rs. 0, okay,
so you will get this facility for the first 5 years,
when you buy your vehicle
with an insurance policy, right, then you will
get it under comprehensive with 50% depreciation and if you have
Zero Dep add-on, then you will
not have to pay a single rupee, right, hope you found this video
informative,
for similar information you can sub-pop the channel, hope
you liked this video,
if you liked the video, then
please like, share the video and subscribe to the channel,
thank you so much,
Jai Hind